Taming a Tank
Hey, Buster Gallon. When did you get to Crest's laboratory? Did you quit farming already?
Absolutely not. Why would I quit when my watermelons are selling like hotcakes?
Yeah, they were delicious.
The Beast Virus that makes Metal Cardbots go berserk... and the vaccine that will conquer that virus.
As a genius scientist and inventor, how could I possibly just sit back and do nothing after hearing the news?
Thanks to him, we're greatly accelerating the development of the vaccine.
See?
- That sounds good and all, but...
- Hi, Mini Gallons!
Ah, and it'd be helpful if Deep Bite could come here, too. How about tomorrow?
Uh, sure! That'll be fine. By the way, there's something I need to tell you.
Hm? What's that?
You see...
W-what?!
My sister transferred to your school?!
We're the ones who were surprised the most, you know.
We had no idea that Soleil was your younger twin sister...
Who on Earth told you that?
Your mom told us, of course!
My mother?!
Dr. Rhea Cayenne! The leading authority on robotics! I even got her autograph!
(So that's how it happened...)
It'll still take some time to develop a vaccine. Until then, take care of my sister.
Uh, wait!
- That didn't go as expected.
- Man...
I was hoping Soleil's brother would have stepped in to resolve the situation...
GRRRRAAHH!!
What was that?!
Grrr!! GRRR!!
I'm gonna crush every single bozo I set my eyes on!!
Stop! This is how you repay me after I fixed and fed you?!
Such a savage.
He hasn’t lost one bit of his wild instincts even after being sealed, I'll give him that.
This isn't the time to be impressed...
Jun! I'll go try to calm Tigun down.
Okay. I'm counting on you.
Stop this, Tigun! There's no need to fight anymore!
Shaddap! Grrrrr!!
I'm-a tiger! A wild tiger listens to nobody!
Blue Cop!
Jun, can't you just keep him in your Metal Breath?
Eheheh... just give me a moment.
Jun! Time for a player substitution!
Uh, I'll go too!
Shut up already!
Uh-
AUGH!
Grrrrrhahaha!! I'm a free tiger now!
Grrrrr!!
- Grrrrhahahaha!!
- Where are you going?!
Huh?!
It's a cat!
Wh-what the heck are you, now? Ya think a little runt like you can take on ME? Tigun?!
Oh, we're doin' this? I'll crush you beneath my feet!
No, Tigun!!
I won't forgive anyone who tries to take a life so carelessly!
Dexter!
It's okay now.
That was a close one, wasn't it?
What gives, Dexter? What brings you to the car center today?
I was working on a building demolition nearby, and I kept hearing the sound of cannon fire coming from the area.
It sounded like it was coming from the direction of Edo's car center, so I rushed over. And what do you know, it was total chaos.
That jerk!
That was one smooth bonk to the head.
You just came here for the cats, didn't you?
The neighborhood cats often gather at uncle Edo's car center, don't they?
Ahem. I suppose that's not untrue...
Either way, it's all thanks to you that it was resolved safely without incident.
What do you mean, "without incident"?! What am I gonna do with that huge mess out there?!
That guy caused me a massive loss!
I'm-a wild tigerrrr....
That's a Wild Cardbot, isn't it? You sealed him?
Yeah. But he still went on a rampage anyway.
You let him go on a rampage like that again, and I'm gonna tell the mayor that we can't get along with the likes of him!
No, you can't!
Wild Cardbot or Metal Cardbot, it doesn't matter anymore. I will banish everyone from the planet Machina! (FX-italic)
B-banish?!
Bye bye~! (FX-italic)
No!! I don't want to break through the atmosphere ever again!
Calm down, Phoenix Fire!
- You hear me?!
- Kitty chose me!
- Sigh... yeah, yeah.
Tigun, come on back.
I'll take him with me. You happy now?
Good grief. You should've done that from the start. Just get him out of here.
I'll leave the checkups on Phoenix Fire and Deep Bite to you, then.
Uh... I'd like you to take a look at my temperature sensor.
I want a full dental scaling, please.
Fine, fine. At least it's better than babysitting a tiger.
Oh! Me first!
Let's go, Blue Cop. Anna, Theo, we're going now!
Jun!
Jun really puts up with a lot, huh.
Yeah...
Anna! Good morning!
Good morning! Uh... Jun?
A-are you okay?
Ugh...
He said he couldn't sleep at all last night.
Really?
Tigun kept on shouting inside the Metal Breath all night long...
Oi! Someone there?! Answer me, now!!
- Be quiet...
- Grrrah!!
- This thing's so cramped, I can't breathe! Get me outta here right now!!!
Do you even realize how late it is?! Shut it!!
It's suffocating in here!!
Get me outta here!
Get me outta here! Let me out!
Get me outta here! Let me out! Letmeoutletmeoutletmeouttahere!!
Get me outta here! Let me out! Letmeoutletmeoutletmeouttahere!! Isaidgetmeouttahere!
Get me outta here! Let me out! Letmeoutletmeoutletmeouttahere!! Isaidgetmeouttahere! Nownownow!!
Get me outta here! Let me out! Letmeoutletmeoutletmeouttahere!! Isaidgetmeouttahere! Nownownow!! Grrrrrrrrr!!!
- Yawn... what's all the racket?
- Get me out!! Grrrrrr!!
Our fridge might be malfunctioning...
Let's have a look...
GRRRAH!!!
AAAHHHH!!
Jun! You can't be putting tigers in the fridge!
This is going to bother the neighbors. Try to fix this somehow...
Okay...
Jun. Jun!
What?
I have an idea.
Eh?
So you took him for a drive all night?
That idiot, Tigun... He kept throwing a tantrum even while we were driving.
That's why I didn't sleep at all last night...
You’re such a fool.
If he won’t listen, just force him to follow your command. Your Metal Breath must have that function, right?
I know. I just don't want to use it.
My mother once said that machines only have value when you use them to their full potential.
They’re not machines! They’re friends!
Friends...?
Yeah! F-R-I-E-N-D-S! They have hearts and feelings, too.
Even if they were born on different planets or come in different sizes, if your hearts connect, you can become friends!
I don’t understand. He doesn’t listen to a word you say, and he doesn't provide you with anything of value. How can you call him a “friend”?
Do you even understand what a friend is?
You calmed down Blue Cop when he went berserk, and you gave him back to me!
...your dearest friend. Right? (FX-italic)
Why did you do that? I thought you understood those feelings between me and Blue Cop!
That was...
Aren't you and Blaion friends?
What?
That is none of your business.
Yes. Yes it is, Blaion. Why do you follow Soleil's-
SHADDAP!!! Just get me outta here!!
Grrrrr!! Grrrrrrrrraahhh!!!
- Dang it, not again! I'll just go back home. Please tell our teacher what happened, guys.
- Get me out!! Lemme out!!
- Ahaha... alright.
- Lemme ouuuuut!!
- Be careful on your way home!
- Grraaaaghhh!!
Blue Cop is my dearest friend! (FX-italic)
Jun is also my dearest friend. (FX-italic)
Looks like you two are really close! (FX-italic)
This car was kept for spare parts... but now look at it. It's not even good enough to be used for scrap now!
How about we get another one for you?
There's a bunch of cars rolling around this town. I'll go grab one for you.
Hey! You can't do that!
I was just messing with you. Hahaha!
I'm back, Edo.
I figured you ran out of these by now. Here you go.
Ugh. Bring it this way.
Thanks for taking care of these homeless kitties, Edo.
Well, I can't exactly kick them out. Until someone comes along to adopt them, they'll be just like family to me.
They're just like you guys in that way, right?
Edo.
Thanks to Jun, I started to think that I can trust humans on this planet.
So please don't push him too hard-
Don't be silly! I took care of him ever since he was as small as a peanut.
I know better than anyone about what he can handle.
He's like family to me too, after all!
By the way, I don't see Nightcrawler...
Night... what? Were you listening to me?
I don't see the black one. You know, the one who tried to fight Tigun.
Don't worry about her. Look. There she is.
Nightcrawler! So that's where you were!
Huh?
Edo, look! I can see why she tried to fight Tigun. Call Jun right away!
Huh? Uh, oh, right.
- What do you want to do today?
- Let's see...
ROAR!!!
Huh?
Was that a tiger?
GRRRRAAARRRR!
- Hey, uncle Edo...
- GRRR! GRRRR!!
- What's up?
- GRRRRRRRRR!!
- Yeah. Yeah...
- GRAAHHHH!! Lemme out lemme out!!
- Are you sure?
- Okay. I'll see you later.
- GRRARRRARRRGHH!!
- Ugh... Alright, Tigun.
- GRAHHH!! Lemme outta here already!! Out!!
- I'll let you out, okay? Just give me a minute.
Wait, really?
Ugh.
Tigun. Come out.
GRAH! Fresh air really is the best!
It's time to go wild aga- eh?
What are you all doing? You guys look like ya wanna fight me or something.
Sounds good to me- What the?
You! Giraffe! You're the one who pulled off a surprise attack on me, aren't ya?!
It was necessary to protect many lives.
Who cares! Sure, I can't use my wild powers at will anymore, but don’t you dare underestimate me! Grrrr-
Hold it. Look here.
Grr? You're the tiny punk who had the nerve to pick a fight with me!
Gah! It's multiplying! Is it using the same technique as Phantom Hornet?!
No...
- Meow!
- Gr-?!
Nightcrawler is a mother. She picked a fight with you because she wanted to protect her children. Do you get it now?
Mo... mother? So what!
Meow!
Gaaahh!
What, you scared of her?
They're so cute, though!
Mothers and fathers alike will do anything to protect their children.
Get away from me! Don't come near!
Those... those eyes...
They look like two suns burning bright through the darkness!
Her eyes reveal a strength of will that’s far greater than mine or any other Wild Cardbot, who only fight for the sake of fighting!
Is this what they call... the resolve of the protector?!
Meow!
Gaaah!! It's too powerful!! Grrrraaahhh!!
Looks like even Wild Cardbots can't beat the power of love.
Tigun. Let's live together on this planet.
Yeah! We should be friends and work together towards a new future!
Friends? I'm just a lone beast that fights until he dies!
Be a lone beast, then.
We'll be your mom and dad, and we'll protect and take care of you until the end.
Tigun.
You can call me mom.
Don't be weird, Blue Cop.
And uncle Edo is your dad!
Eh?!
P-protect me? Bwahahahaha!
I am a Wild Cardbot! You'll never know when I might bare my claws against you Metal Cardbots, my eternal foes!
If you do that, I'll just blame my poor judgement and give up on you!
Wh-?!
- Oh...
- Jun! That isn't something to joke about!
I believe in you, Tigun. So please, believe in me too!
Grrrr... Protect me, huh...?
Guess it can't hurt to try living a life where fighting isn't everything.
Thank you, Tigun- Oh!
Meow! Meow!
W-wait, wait- Ow!!
First he'll need to learn how to get along with Nightcrawler.
Hahahaha!
Hm. I came here because I smelled a fight brewing with Mr. Tigun,
but what in the world am I looking at? Being all warmhearted and friendly...
What a disappointment!
Not like that! Act like you're on a real hunt! Chomp it! Pounce on it and chomp it!
That's right! Use your claws too! Pull out your full arsenal!
What in the world happened here?
The same Tigun that only knew how to rampage, is now playing with kittens.
He looks like a dad playing with his babies.
He's better than my dad!
Alright, kids! The great Tigun will teach ya what a real hunt looks like!
ROAR!!
Meow!
GRRRRRRRRR!!
Meowmeowmeowmeow!
Hey, hey, just don't break anything around here, alright?
Okay, Papa Edo!
I said call me big bro Edo! Big bro!!
Follow me! Time for the next lesson!
ROARRRR!!
Meow!